tuebl.com 2017-06-21

# EbookBike - Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy:

#### Information Collected

Our Site collects information regarding domain names, IP address (static or dynamic IP-address that sometimes point to a particular identifiable computer or device), type of browser, operating system, time of access and referring/exit web site addresses. This information is used by EbookBike. for operational purposes, to maintain service quality and to track site trends and statistics. Most of the time, this information does not personally identify you. This information may be stored on our servers or the servers of third party analtyics providers surch as Google Analytics (our current partner). This is subject to change. 

We also collect any personal information that you choose to provide when you use this Site. This may include, but is not limited to the events when you: create an account, order and/or download products, contact our sales department, post content in our forums or interact with other areas of our support center. This information of personal nature may include, your name, e-mail address, and any other information selected by you to share. We may collect any additional personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide through such posting, contact or interaction, in cases when you post content in the forums, interact with other areas of our support center, or contact our sales department or support teams, In case you sign up for any EbookBike newsletter, webinar, survey, other communication or you just want to make general contact with us, we will collect information of your contact to fulfill your request. In case you wan to unsubscribe, follow the unsubscribe link that appears at the end of each communication or, you may unsubscribe via your account preferences. Unsubscribing will remove you from any further communication but does not garuntee your removal from our database. To be completely deleted from our database emailing us at info@ebook.bike is the best course. 

#### Use, Sharing or Disclosing of Personal Information

Please note that we do not sell or rent your personal information to any third party. The main purpose we use your personal for is to communicate with you in the most efficient manner. We may share, disclose, or provide your personal information with or to a third party: (i) in cases when we attempt to collect a payment or debt, (ii) when we are required to combat fraud or to protect our interests, (iii) in order to enforce the Terms of Use of this Site or other EbookBike. Sites, (iv) in cases when we are required to do so by law or in order to respond to legal process or lawful requests, including from law enforcement or government agencies, (v) within and among our affiliates and subsidiaries, or (vi) as part of a merger or sale of a business. We may use or share your personal information for the purpose of delivering correspondence, communications, or services, such as newsletters, events, training or software that you request or purchase, as well as to make a notification to you about the status of your order. Any information you have provided may be used by us for the purpose of providing customer support to you. Note that, these third parties are authorized to use your personal information ONLY for the sole purpose of providing these services to us. 

#### Use of Cookies

Please note: Basically every website you will ever use ever uses cookies. It's a fact of using the Internet in a modern time. Laws that require a "cookie notice" are bullshit and only create a false sense of security in people using websites that don't comply with the laws. If you are on the internet, assume there are cookies involved.

Cookies are used by us occasionally. In their nature Cookies are small text files that can be used by a web site to identify/recognize a repeat visitor to the web site. Cookies may be used by us for variable reasons, including: 

  * To facilitate the navigation of our website
  * To help the sign up and login process for our services
  * To make your experience personalized
  * For analysis of page frequency visitation
  * In order to provide social sharing widgets and videos features of the website
  * To be able to measure effectiveness of advertising and promotions

In case you do not wish EbookBike. to deploy cookies in your browser, you can opt out by changing your browser settings to reject cookies or to notify you when a web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. When possible EbookBike tries to respect DNT tokens in your browser. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, our Site can still be used by you but your ability to use some of the products and/or services at this site may be affected and full site functionality is not guaranteed. 

#### Information Security

We make sure that appropriate security measures are taken to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, use or disclosure. Among these measures are a variety of security technologies and procedures like data collection internal reviews, practices regarding storage and processing and also security measures and appropriate encryption and physical security measures. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) certificates to encrypt the transmission of data on the EbookBike. payment and login pages. Please note that no transmission via the internet can be fully secure, therefore, on your side you are also responsible for taking the necessary measures for protection of your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, including protection of your password. Apart from the indications under “Use, Sharing or Disclosing of Personal Information”, access to your personal information is restricted ONLY to EbookBike. employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information so that they can process it and provide personalized customer support to you. Note that these individuals are bound by strict confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination in case they fail to comply with these complications. 

#### Credit Card Processing

A third-party service provider is used by us to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use your personal information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.
